<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Material Components Demo</string>
    <string name="search_component_hint">Search material component</string>
    <string name="action_search_title">Search component</string>

    <string name="banner_description">Material Component Banner</string>

    <!--Text Field strings-->

    <string name="text_field_title">Text fields</string>
    <string name="text_field_span_title"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h1>Text fields</h1>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields let users enter and edit text.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Usage</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields allow users to enter text into a UI. They typically appear in forms and dialogs.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_types"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Types</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields come in two types:
                <ul>
                    <li>Filled text fields
                    <li>Outlined text fields
                </ul>
                Both types of text fields use a container to provide , making the fields discoverable in layouts.
                Both types of text fields provide the same functionality: a clear affordance for interaction. The type of text field you use can depend on style alone.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_filled"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Filled text field</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Filled text fields have more visual emphasis than outlined text fields, making them stand out when surrounded by other content and components.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_outlined"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Outlined text field</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Outlined text fields have less visual emphasis than filled text fields. When they appear in places like forms, where many text fields are placed together, their reduced emphasis helps simplify the layout.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_icon"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Icons</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Icons in text fields are optional. Text field icons can describe valid input methods (such as a microphone icon), provide affordances to access additional functionality (such as clearing the content of a field), and can express an error.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_label_filled">Filled text field</string>
    <string name="text_field_label_outlined">Outlined text field</string>
    <string name="text_field_label_password">Password</string>
    <string name="text_field_error">Password can\'t be shorter than 8 characters</string>
    <string name="text_field_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="text_field_toast">Password suitable</string>
    <!--Bottom navigation strings-->
    <string name="bottom_navigation_title">Bottom navigation</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_title"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        <h1>Bottom navigation</h1>
    </p>
    <p>Bottom navigation bars allow movement between primary destinations in an app.</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_usage"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        <h1>Usage</h1>
    </p>
    <p>Bottom navigation bars display three to five destinations at the bottom of a screen. Each destination is represented by an icon and an optional text label. When a bottom navigation icon is tapped, the user is taken to the top-level navigation destination associated with that icon.</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_when_to_use"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>When to use</h3>
            </p>
            <p>Bottom navigation should be used for:
        <ul>
          <li>  Top-level destinations that need to be accessible from anywhere in the app
          <li>  Three to five destinations
           <li> Mobile or tablet only
        </ul>
        Bottom navigation shouldn’t be used for:
        <ul>
          <li>  Single tasks, such as viewing a single email
          <li>  User preferences or settings
        </ul>
        </p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_behavior"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        <h3>Behavior</h3>
    </p>
    <p>Bottom navigation behaves differently on Android and iOS. When you select a bottom navigation item (one that’s not currently selected), each platform displays different outcomes:
<ul>
 <li>   On Android: the app navigates to a destination’s top-level screen. Any prior user interactions and temporary screen states are reset, such as scroll position, tab selection, and in-line search.
  <li>  On iOS: the destination reflects the user’s prior interaction. If the user previously visited that section of the app, they return to the last screen viewed (with its prior state preserved, if possible). Otherwise, the app navigates to the top-level screen.
</ul>
Default platform navigation can be overridden when needed to improve the user experience. For example, an Android app that requires frequent switching between sections can preserve each section’s state. Or, an iOS app can return users to the top-level screen (or reset their scroll position) if it better suits the use case.</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_state"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        <h1>States</h1>
    </p>
    <p>Bottom navigation destinations may be active, inactive, focused or pressed.

Bottom navigation uses opacity and text to show when a destination is active. States are used to show pressed, focused, and unselected states.

Inactive destination states are represented with reduced opacities; active states have full opacity.
Side by side view of two examples of bottom navigation, highlighting the difference between inactive and active destinations.</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_page_favorite">Page favorite</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_home">Home</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_page_music">Page music</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_music">Music</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_page_places">Page places</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_places">Places</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_page_news">Page news</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_page_home">Page home</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_news">News</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_picture_places">Picture places</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_picture_news">Picture news</string>
    <string name="bottom_navigation_span_picture_guitar">Picture guitar</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>
