<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Material Components Demo</string>
    <string name="search_component_hint">Search material component</string>
    <string name="action_search_title">Search component</string>

    <string name="banner_description">Material Component Banner</string>

    <!--Text Field strings-->

    <string name="text_field_title">Text fields</string>
    <string name="text_field_span_title"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h1>Text fields</h1>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields let users enter and edit text.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Usage</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields allow users to enter text into a UI. They typically appear in forms and dialogs.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_types"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Types</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields come in two types:
                <ul>
                    <li>Filled text fields
                    <li>Outlined text fields
                </ul>
                Both types of text fields use a container to provide , making the fields discoverable in layouts.
                Both types of text fields provide the same functionality: a clear affordance for interaction. The type of text field you use can depend on style alone.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_filled"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Filled text field</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Filled text fields have more visual emphasis than outlined text fields, making them stand out when surrounded by other content and components.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_outlined"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Outlined text field</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Outlined text fields have less visual emphasis than filled text fields. When they appear in places like forms, where many text fields are placed together, their reduced emphasis helps simplify the layout.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_icon"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Icons</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Icons in text fields are optional. Text field icons can describe valid input methods (such as a microphone icon), provide affordances to access additional functionality (such as clearing the content of a field), and can express an error.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_label_filled">Filled text field</string>
    <string name="text_field_label_outlined">Outlined text field</string>
    <string name="text_field_label_password">Password</string>
    <string name="text_field_error">Password can\'t be shorter than 8 characters</string>
    <string name="text_field_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="text_field_toast">Password suitable</string>


    <!--Button strings-->

    <string name="button_title">Buttons</string>
    <string name="button_span_title"><![CDATA[
            <p>
            <h1>Buttons</h1>
            </p>
            <p>Buttons allow users to take actions, and make choices, with a single tap.</p> ]]>
         </string>
    <string name="button_span_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>        <h3>Usage</h3>        </p>
            <p>Buttons communicate actions that users can take. They are typically placed throughout your UI, in places like:
            <ul>
                <li>Dialogs
                <li>Modal windows
                <li>Forms
                <li>Cards
                <li>Toolbars
            </ul>        .</p>        ]]>
        </string>
    <string name="button_span_anatomy"><![CDATA[
            <p>        <h3>Anatomy</h3>        </p>
            <p>Buttons contain one required element and four optional elements.</p>        ]]>
        </string>
    <string name="button_span_hierarchy"><![CDATA[
            <p>        <h3>Hierarchy</h3>        </p>
            <p><h5>A single, prominent button</h5></p>
            <p>A layout should contain a single prominent button that makes it clear that other buttons have less importance in the hierarchy. This high-emphasis button commands the most attention.</p>
            <p><h5>Other buttons</h5></p>
            <p>An app can show more than one button in a layout at a time, so a high-emphasis button can be accompanied by medium- and low-emphasis buttons that perform less important actions. When using multiple buttons, ensure the available state of one button doesn’t look like the disabled state of another.</p>]]>
         </string>
    <string name="button_span_placement"><![CDATA[
            <p>        <h3>Placement</h3>        </p>
            <p>Multiple button types can be used to express different emphasis levels.</p>    ]]>
        </string>
    <string name="button_span_text_button_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>        <h3>Text button usage</h3>        </p>
            <p>Text buttons are typically used for less-pronounced actions, including those located:
            <ul>
               <li> In dialogs
               <li> In cards
             </ul>
             In cards, text buttons help maintain an emphasis on card content.</p>]]>
        </string>
    <string name="button_span_outlined_button_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>        <h3>Outlined button usage</h3>        </p>
            <p>Outlined buttons are medium-emphasis buttons. They contain actions that are important, but aren’t the primary action in an app.</p>    ]]>
        </string>
    <string name="button_span_contained_button_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>        <h3>Contained button usage</h3>        </p>
            <p>Contained buttons are high-emphasis, distinguished by their use of elevation and fill. They contain actions that are primary to your app.</p>    ]]>
        </string>
    <string name="button_span_toggle_button_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>        <h3>Toggle button usage</h3>        </p>
            <p>Toggle buttons can be used to group related options. To emphasize groups of related toggle buttons, a group should share a common container.</p>    ]]>
        </string>
    <string name="button_text_button">Text button</string>
    <string name="button_outlined_button">Outlined button</string>
    <string name="button_contained_button">Contained button</string>
    <string name="button_toggle_button_usage">Toggle button usage</string>
    <string name="button_have_press_outlined_button"> Have press outlined button</string>
    <string name="button_have_press_text_button"> Have press text button</string>
    <string name="button_have_press_contained_button"> Have press contained button</string>
    <!--Slider strings-->
    <string name="slider_title">Slider</string>
    <string name="slider_span_title"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                 <h1>Slider</h1>
            </p>
            <p>
            Sliders allow users to make selections from a range of values.
            </p>
        ]]>
        </string>
    <string name="slider_span_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                 <h3>Usage</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
            Sliders reflect a range of values along a bar, from which users may select a single value. They are ideal for adjusting settings such as volume, brightness, or applying image filters.
            </p>
        ]]>
        </string>
    <string name="slider_span_anatomy"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                 <h3>Anatomy</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
            A slider can contain the following elements:Track shows the range available for user selection. For left-to-right (LTR) languages, the smallest value appears on the far left, and the largest value on the far right. For right-to-left (RTL) languages this orientation is reversed, with the smallest value on the far right and the largest value on the far left;Thumb slides along the track, displaying the selected value through its position;Value label (optional) displays the currently selected, specific numerical value.Tick mark (optional)represent predetermined values to which the user can move the slider.
            </p>
        ]]>
        </string>
    <string name="slider_span_continuous"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                 <h3>Continuous slider</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
            Use continuous sliders allow users to make meaningful selections that don’t require a specific value.
            </p>
        ]]>
        </string>
    <string name="slider_span_discrete"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                 <h3>Discrete slider</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
            Discrete sliders display a numeric value label upon pressing the thumb, which allows a user to input an exact value.
            </p>
        ]]>
     </string>
</resources>
