<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Material Components Demo</string>
    <string name="search_component_hint">Search material component</string>
    <string name="action_search_title">Search component</string>

    <string name="banner_description">Material Component Banner</string>

    <!--Text Field strings-->

    <string name="text_field_title">Text fields</string>
    <string name="text_field_span_title"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h1>Text fields</h1>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields let users enter and edit text.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Usage</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields allow users to enter text into a UI. They typically appear in forms and dialogs.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_types"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Types</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields come in two types:
                <ul>
                    <li>Filled text fields
                    <li>Outlined text fields
                </ul>
                Both types of text fields use a container to provide , making the fields discoverable in layouts.
                Both types of text fields provide the same functionality: a clear affordance for interaction. The type of text field you use can depend on style alone.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_filled"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Filled text field</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Filled text fields have more visual emphasis than outlined text fields, making them stand out when surrounded by other content and components.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_outlined"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Outlined text field</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Outlined text fields have less visual emphasis than filled text fields. When they appear in places like forms, where many text fields are placed together, their reduced emphasis helps simplify the layout.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_icon"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Icons</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Icons in text fields are optional. Text field icons can describe valid input methods (such as a microphone icon), provide affordances to access additional functionality (such as clearing the content of a field), and can express an error.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_label_filled">Filled text field</string>
    <string name="text_field_label_outlined">Outlined text field</string>
    <string name="text_field_label_password">Password</string>
    <string name="text_field_error">Password can\'t be shorter than 8 characters</string>
    <string name="text_field_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="text_field_toast">Password suitable</string>


    <!--Card strings-->

    <string name="card_title">Card</string>
    <string name="card_span_title"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h1>Card</h1>
            </p>
            <p>
                Cards contain content and actions about a single subject.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="card_span_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Usage</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Cards are surfaces that display content and actions on a single topic.<br><br>
                They should be easy to scan for relevant and actionable information. Elements, like text and images, should be placed on them in a way that clearly indicates hierarchy.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="card_span_gestures"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Gestures</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
              Gestures should be implemented consistently within a card collection. Frequently used gestures on cards include swipe, pick up and move, and scrolling.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="card_span_gestures_swipe"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h4>Swipe</h4>
            </p>
            <p>
                A swipe gesture can be performed on a single card at a time, anywhere on that card.<br>
                <br>It can be used to:
            </p>

             <ul>
                    <li>Dismiss a card</li>
                    <li>Change the state of a card (such as flagging or archiving it)</li>
             </ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="card_span_gestures_scrolling"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h4>Scrolling</h4>
            </p>
            <p>
                Card content that is taller than the maximum card height is truncated and does not scroll, but can be displayed by expanding the height of a card. A card can expand beyond the maximum height of the screen, in which case the card scrolls within the screen.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="card_sample_description">Greyhould divisively hello coldly wonderfully marginally far upon excluding</string>
    <string name="card_sample_title">Title</string>
    <string name="card_sample_secondtext">Secondary text</string>
    <string name="card_sample_action1">action 1</string>
    <string name="card_sample_action2">action 2</string>
    <string name="card_sample_image_description">content_description_media</string>

    <string name="card_sample_clicked_button1">Action 1 button clicked!</string>
    <string name="card_sample_clicked_button2">Action 2 button clicked!</string>


</resources>
