<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Material Components Demo</string>
    <string name="search_component_hint">Search material component</string>
    <string name="action_search_title">Search component</string>

    <string name="banner_description">Material Component Banner</string>

    <!--Text Field strings-->

    <string name="text_field_title">Text fields</string>
    <string name="text_field_span_title"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h1>Text fields</h1>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields let users enter and edit text.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Usage</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields allow users to enter text into a UI. They typically appear in forms and dialogs.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_types"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Types</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields come in two types:
                <ul>
                    <li>Filled text fields
                    <li>Outlined text fields
                </ul>
                Both types of text fields use a container to provide , making the fields discoverable in layouts.
                Both types of text fields provide the same functionality: a clear affordance for interaction. The type of text field you use can depend on style alone.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_filled"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Filled text field</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Filled text fields have more visual emphasis than outlined text fields, making them stand out when surrounded by other content and components.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_outlined"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Outlined text field</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Outlined text fields have less visual emphasis than filled text fields. When they appear in places like forms, where many text fields are placed together, their reduced emphasis helps simplify the layout.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_icon"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Icons</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Icons in text fields are optional. Text field icons can describe valid input methods (such as a microphone icon), provide affordances to access additional functionality (such as clearing the content of a field), and can express an error.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_label_filled">Filled text field</string>
    <string name="text_field_label_outlined">Outlined text field</string>
    <string name="text_field_label_password">Password</string>
    <string name="text_field_error">Password can\'t be shorter than 8 characters</string>
    <string name="text_field_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="text_field_toast">Password suitable</string>

    <!-- Menu strings-->
    <string name="menu_title">Menu</string>
    <string name="menu_span_title"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h1>Menu</h1>
            </p>
            <p>
                Menus display a list of choices on temporary surfaces.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="menu_span_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Usage</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                A menu displays a list of choices on a temporary surface. They appear when users interact with a button, action, or other control.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="menu_span_types"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Types</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Menus allow users to make a selection from multiple options. They are less prominent and take up less space than selection controls, such as a set of radio buttons.
                <ul>
                <li> Dropdown menus display a list of options, triggered by an icon, button, or action. Their placement varies based on the element that opens them.
                <li> Exposed dropdown menus display the currently selected menu item above the list of options. Some variations can accept user-entered input.
                </ul>
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="menu_span_placement"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Placement</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Menus appear in front of all other permanent UI elements.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="menu_span_dropdown"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Dropdown menu</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                A dropdown menu is a compact way of displaying multiple choices. It appears upon interaction with an element (such as an icon or button) or when users perform a specific action.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="menu_span_exposed_dropdown"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Exposed Dropdown menu</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Exposed dropdown menus display the currently selected menu item above the menu. They can be used only when a single menu item can be chosen at a time.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="menu_headset">Headset</string>
    <string name="menu_star">Star</string>
    <string name="menu_music_note">Music note</string>
    <string name="menu_info">Info</string>
</resources>
