<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Material Components Demo</string>
    <string name="search_component_hint">Search material component</string>
    <string name="action_search_title">Search component</string>

    <string name="banner_description">Material Component Banner</string>

    <!--Text Field strings-->

    <string name="text_field_title">Text fields</string>
    <string name="text_field_span_title"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h1>Text fields</h1>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields let users enter and edit text.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Usage</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields allow users to enter text into a UI. They typically appear in forms and dialogs.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_types"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Types</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Text fields come in two types:
                <ul>
                    <li>Filled text fields
                    <li>Outlined text fields
                </ul>
                Both types of text fields use a container to provide , making the fields discoverable in layouts.
                Both types of text fields provide the same functionality: a clear affordance for interaction. The type of text field you use can depend on style alone.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_filled"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Filled text field</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Filled text fields have more visual emphasis than outlined text fields, making them stand out when surrounded by other content and components.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_outlined"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Outlined text field</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Outlined text fields have less visual emphasis than filled text fields. When they appear in places like forms, where many text fields are placed together, their reduced emphasis helps simplify the layout.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_span_icon"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Icons</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Icons in text fields are optional. Text field icons can describe valid input methods (such as a microphone icon), provide affordances to access additional functionality (such as clearing the content of a field), and can express an error.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="text_field_label_filled">Filled text field</string>
    <string name="text_field_label_outlined">Outlined text field</string>
    <string name="text_field_label_password">Password</string>
    <string name="text_field_error">Password can\'t be shorter than 8 characters</string>
    <string name="text_field_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="text_field_toast">Password suitable</string>


    <!--Dialogs strings-->

    <string name="dialog_title">Dialog</string>
    <string name="dialog_span_title"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h1>Dialogs</h1>
            </p>
            <p>
                Dialogs inform users about a task and can contain critical information, require decisions, or involve multiple tasks.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_span_usage"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Usage</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                A dialog is a type of modal window that appears in front of app content to provide critical information or ask for a decision. Dialogs disable all app functionality when they appear, and remain on screen until confirmed, dismissed, or a required action has been taken.
                <br><br>
                Dialogs are purposefully interruptive, so they should be used sparingly.
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_span_when_to_use"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>When to use</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Dialogs should be used for:<br>
                <ul>
                <li>Errors that block an app’s normal operation</li>
                <li>Critical information that requires a specific user task, decision, or acknowledgement</li>
                </ul>
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_span_types"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h4>Types</h4>
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_span_types_alert"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Alert Dialog</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Alert dialogs interrupt users with urgent information, details, or actions.<br>
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_span_types_simple"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Simple Dialog</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
               Simple dialogs can display items that are immediately actionable when selected. They don’t have text buttons.
               <br><br>
               As simple dialogs are interruptive, they should be used sparingly. Alternatively, dropdown menus provide options in a non-modal, less disruptive way.</p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="dialog_span_types_confirmation"><![CDATA[
            <p>
                <h3>Confirmation Dialog</h3>
            </p>
            <p>
                Confirmation dialogs give users the ability to provide final confirmation of a choice before committing to it, so they have a chance to change their minds if necessary.
                <br><br>
                If the user confirms a choice, it’s carried out. Otherwise, the user can dismiss the dialog. For example, users can listen to multiple ringtones but only make a final selection upon tapping “OK.”
            </p>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="dialog_alert_button">ALERT DIALOG</string>
    <string name="dialog_simple_button">SIMPLE DIALOG</string>
    <string name="dialog_confirmation_button">CONFIRMATION DIALOG</string>

    <string name="dialog_alert_discard">DISCARD</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_cancel">CANCEL</string>
    <string name="dialog_alert_draft">Discard Draft?</string>

    <string name="dialog_simple_option">View options</string>
    <string name="dialog_simple_accept">ACCEPT</string>

    <string name="dialog_confirmation_ringtone">Phone Ringtone</string>
    <string name="dialog_confirmation_ok">OK</string>

    <string-array name="dialog_array_simple">
        <item>Photos</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>All</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="dialog_array_confirmation">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Callisto</item>
        <item>Ganymede</item>
        <item>Luna</item>
        <item>Oberon</item>
        <item>Phobos</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
